Guide to the Frank Whitson Fetter Papers, 1902-1992
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Commissions, Consulting and Government Services, 1924-1974 (bulk 1924-1930). (Box 7)
  - State Department: German Debt Settlement, 1950-1953 (Box 11)
    - Oral History interview: Government service, 1974 (Box 11)
    - U.S. Department of State: Correspondence: Employment, 1941-1942, 1946 (Box 11)
- Northwestern University, 1947-1968. (Box 11)
  Arranged in three subseries: Courses (1947-1967), Committees (1954-1964), and Miscellaneous (1960-1966). Courses, arranged alphabetically, include assignments, bibliographies, syllabi, exams, grade books, handwritten and typed research notes, as well as correspondence and memos regarding his classes. Files documenting Fetter's committee work and other university activities contain correspondence, research notes, reports, and programs.
  - Courses (Box 11)
    - Ford Summer Seminar: (Box 11)
      - Correspondence: (Box 11)
        - 1957-1961 (Box 11)
        - Seminar attendees, 1957-1958 (Box 11)
      - Memos, 1957-1958 (Box 11)
      - Notes: miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 11)
    - Grade books, 1948-1951 (Box 11)
    - Grade books, 1965-1965, (5 folders) (Box 12)
    - History of Economic Theory (ECD18): (Box 12)
      - Bibliography: (Box 12)
        - History of Economic Analysis, 1958, undated (Box 12)
        - International Economic papers, 1963, undated (Box 12)
      - Exams, grades, miscellaneous, syllabus, 1962-1967, undated, (4 folders) (Box 12)
      - Notes: (Box 12)
        - Economic growth, 1958-1967, undated (Box 12)
        - History of Economics, 1955-1966, undated (Box 12)
        - Manderville and Hume, 1953-1963, undated (Box 12)
        - Mathematical Economics, Cournot, Gossen, Jevons, 1963, 1967 (Box 12)
        - Miscellaneous, 1935-1980s, undated (Box 12)
        - Petty, 1956-1967, undated (Box 12)
        - Ricardo, 1921-1967, undated (Box 12)
        - Ruskin, etc., 1934, 1966, undated (Box 12)
        - Young, Arthur (Box 12)
      - Reading lists, miscellaneous, 1966, 1967 (Box 12)
    - History of Economic Thought (EcC20): (Box 12)
      - Class records, 1949-1963, undated (Box 12)
      - Notes: Karl Marx, 1953-1967, undated (Box 12)
    - History of Economic Thought/Theory (EcC20, EcD18) (Box 12)
      - Clippings, miscellaneous, 1962, undated (Box 12)
      - Notes: (Box 12)
        - Cantillion, 1953-1954, 1967, undated (Box 12)
        - Medieval economic thought, 1953, 1967 (Box 12)
        - Physiocrats, 1931-1956, undated (Box 12)
    - International Economic Policy (EcD61) (Box 12)
      - Bibliography: (Box 12)
        - Doctoral thesis in International Relations and Economic Development, 1946-1956, 1957 (Box 12)
        - Economic development, undated (Box 12)
      - Clippings: Reparations and War Debt, undated (Box 12)
      - Exams, assignments, miscellaneous, 1961-1963, 1966, undated (Box 12)
      - Notes: (Box 12)
        - Adjustment to tariff reductions, 1962-1963, 1965, undated (Box 12)
        - Alliance for Progress, 1962-1963, undated (Box 12)
        - Balance of payments, 1961, 1966, undated (Box 12)
        - Brookings BOP study, reading lists, 1963-1965 (Box 12)
        - Commercial treaties, 1950-1966, undated (Box 12)
    - International Economic Policy (EcD61) (Box 12)
      - Notes: (Box 12)
        - The Economic “Miracles”: Finland, Germany, Italy, Japan, 1966-1967, undated (Box 12)
        - General Agreement of Tariffs and Trade (GATT), 1965-1966, undated (Box 12)
        - Import Reducing and Export Increasing proposals, 1959 (Box 12)
        - International Income Comparisons, 1957-1963, undated (Box 12)
        - Measuring Height of Tariff, 1965, undated (Box 12)
        - Rise of the New Lending Agencies, 1947-1965, undated (Box 12)
        - South American and Central American Common Market, 1965 (Box 12)
        - Stabilization of Export Earnings, 1962-1963, undated (Box 12)
        - Terms of Trade, 1956-1965, undated (Box 12)
        - Trade Expansion Act of 1962, 1962-1968 (Box 12)
      - Opening lecture, 1963, 1966 (Box 12)
      - Readings: European Free Trade area, 1955-1965, undated (Box 12)
    - International Economic Problems (Dartmouth) (EC49): Assignments, exams, grade book, readings, 1925-1949, undated (Box 12)
    - International Economic Problems (Dartmouth)/Policy (EC49, EcD61): (Box 12)
      - Clippings, Common Market, 1964, undated (Box 12)
      - Notes and readings: East-West Trade, 1960-1968 (Box 12)
    - International Economic Problems (Dartmouth)/Policy (EC49, EcD61): (Box 12)
      - Notes: (Box 12)
        - European Common Market, 1959-1968, undated (Box 12)
        - Good tariff, infant industry, Argument, 1963, undated (Box 12)
        - Miscellaneous, readings, 1966-1968, undated (Box 12)
        - Preferential tariffs, 1963-1968, undated (Box 12)
        - Private boycotts on International Trade, local legislation, 1946-1968, undated (Box 12)
        - Tariff classification, 1963-1968, undated (Box 12)
        - Tariff Commission investigation, 1967-1968, undated (Box 12)
    - International Economic Problems (Dartmouth)/Policy (EC49, EcD61): (Box 13)
      - Notes: Theory of Customs Unions, 1962-1968, undated (Box 13)
    - International Economic Relations (EcC10): Photograph, readings, 1948 (Box 13)
    - International Economic Relations/Value and Distribution (EcC10, EcD1): (Box 13)
      - Assignments, syllabi, 1947,summer (Box 13)
    - International Investment (EcC60, EcC51): (Box 13)
      - Exams, 1952-1961 (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1951, undated (Box 13)
      - Notes: (Box 13)
        - America's Experience as a Debtor and Creditor Country, 1949-1961, undated (Box 13)
        - Capital Intensity and Foreign Investment, 1935-1960, undated (Box 13)
        - Economic theory, 1923, undated (Box 13)
        - Export Industries and Debt Payment, typing of loan proceeds, 1951-1958, undated (Box 13)
        - Foreign language, 1962, undated (Box 13)
        - The Forms of Foreign Investment, 1953-1956 (Box 13)
        - Foreign Investment (Box 13)
        - International Finance, 1922-1956, undated (Box 13)
        - Keynes, 1932-1950, undated (Box 13)
        - The Motives for Foreign Investment, 1936-1958, undated (Box 13)
    - International Investment (EcC60, EcC51): (Box 13)
      - Notes: (Box 13)
        - Adam Smith on Foreign Trade, undated (Box 13)
        - Transfer of Foreign Loans, 1949-1961, undated (Box 13)
      - Opening Lectures, 1953-1960, undated (Box 13)
      - Readings, Foreign Investments in relation to Capital Industry, 1943-1946 (Box 13)
    - International Trade and Finance (EcB60, EcC06): (Box 13)
      - Assignments, Miscellaneous, 1962, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
      - Clippings, Foreign Investment (Private), 1927-1937, undated (Box 13)
      - Exams: (Box 13)
        - Notes: Sources of information on International Economic Relations, 1962 (Box 13)
        - Readings, miscellaneous, 1957-1966 (Box 13)
      - Notes: (Box 13)
        - Alternative Methods of Adjustment in Balance of Payments, 1949-1966, undated (Box 13)
        - Bullion Reports, undated (Box 13)
        - Customs Valuation, undated (Box 13)
        - Dumping, undated (Box 13)
        - The Economic Consequences of Mr. Churchill, 1959, 1962 (Box 13)
        - Effect on Tariff on Prices, 1962-1966, undated (Box 13)
        - European Trade Areas, 1959-1966 (Box 13)
        - Foreign Exchange, 1956-1968, undated (Box 13)
        - International Competitive Situation of Steel, 1933-1966, undated (Box 13)
        - Main features of U.S. Foreign Trade, 1965-1968 (Box 13)
        - Main features of International World Trade, 1965 (Box 13)
        - Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 13)
        - Price of Gold, 1960, 1962 (Box 13)
        - Reciprocal Trade Agreements program, 1961-1966, undated (Box 13)
        - Silver, undated (Box 13)
        - Steel Imports, 1962-1968, undated (Box 13)
        - Sterling area: Rise of Imperial Preference, 1956-1960 (Box 13)
        - Trade Agreements program, 1960 (Box 13)
      - Opening lecture: Special Features of International Trade and Finance, 1933-1966, undated (Box 13)
    - Latin American Culture and Civilization (C1): Notes, syllabus, 1949-1950 undated (Box 13)
    - Medill School of Journalism: Editorial Operations (E02): Notes for talk: European Common Market, 1958-1965, undated (Box 13)
    - Monetary Institutions and Policies (EcD31): (Box 13)
      - Exam, readings, syllabus, 1964-19677, (2 folders) (Box 13)
      - Notes: (Box 13)
        - American Controversy and the Federal Reserve, 1962-1964, undated (Box 13)
        - Bagehot Principle, 1962--1963, 1966, undated (Box 13)
        - The Bank Act of 1844, 1962-1966, undated (Box 13)
        - Committee on Money and Credit, 1958, 1960-1965, undated (Box 13)
        - Credit Cards and new forms of Consumer Credit, 1966, undated (Box 13)
        - Details on Coins and Bank Notes--Counterfeiting, 1963, 1965, undated (Box 13)
        - Gold Production and Prices, 1964, 1968 (Box 13)
        - Macmillan Report, 1936-1962, undated (Box 13)
        - Miscellaneous, 1964-1966 (Box 13)
        - Monetary Policy of World War I and the 1920s and 1930s, 1962 (Box 13)
        - Price of Silver, 1962-1967, undated (Box 13)
    - National Income Distribution (EcC85, EcC23, Ec83,): (Box 13)
      - Assignments, exams, readings, syllabus, 1950-1960, (2 folders) (Box 13)
      - Exams, syllabus, 1948-1949 (Box 13)
      - Notes: (Box 13)
        - Definition of Income, 1948-1954, undated (Box 13)
        - Government Operations and Transfer Payments, 1952, undated (Box 13)
        - Miscellaneous, 1948-1954, undated, (2 folders) (Box 13)
        - Sources of Data, 1950-1953 (Box 13)
      - Opening lecture: National Income, 1950-1960 (Box 13)
    - Ph.D. Exams: (Box 13)
      - History of Theory, 1952-1959 (Box 13)
      - International Economics, 1949-1963, undated (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1967 (Box 13)
      - Money and Banking, 1962-1963 (Box 13)
    - Problems in Money and Banking (Dartmouth)/Monetary Institutions and Policies (Ec46, EcC31): (Box 14)
      - Notes: (Box 14)
        - American Treasure and its consequences, 1963, undated (Box 14)
        - Aspects of Policies and Institutions, 1962, 1964, undated (Box 14)
        - The Bullion Controversy, 1932-1967, undated (Box 14)
        - Bimentalism and the Gold and Silver Commission, 1962-1966, undated (Box 14)
        - British Experience in World War I and Interwar Years, 1962-1967, undated (Box 14)
        - The Gold Standard for the Bagehot Principle to 1914, 1966-1967, undated (Box 14)
        - International Monetary Fund and the Aftermath of World War II, 1962-1967 (Box 14)
        - Monetary Theory and Policy, 1962-1967, undated (Box 14)
        - Proposals for International Monetary Reform, 1959, 1962-1967, undated, (2 folders) (Box 14)
        - Radcliff Report, 1959-1967, undated (Box 14)
    - Problems in Money and Banking (Dartmouth) (Ec46): (Box 14)
      - Assignments, syllabi, 1967-1968 (Box 14)
      - Exams and grades, 1967-1968 (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous, 1967, undated (Box 14)
      - Notes: (Box 14)
        - British Devaluation, 1963, 1967 (Box 14)
        - Book lists, exams, notes, 1962-1968, undated (Box 14)
    - Problem of Economic Instability (ECB01, B03): Notes: Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 14)
    - Research Seminar in International Economic Relations and Development: (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous, readings, 1952-1966, undated (Box 14)
    - Scrittori Classici Italiani, undated (Box 14)
    - Seminar on Methods of Economic Research (Ec83): Readings, syllabus, 1967-1968, undated (Box 14)
    - Seminar on Methods of Economic Research/Seniors Honor Seminar (Ec83, EcC98): (Box 14)
      - Notes: (Box 14)
        - Economic Prediction, 1964-1968, undated (Box 14)
        - Interpretation of Data, 1966-1968, undated (Box 14)
    - Senior Honors Seminar (EcC98): (Box 14)
      - Assignments, readings, syllabus, 1964-1967, undated, (2 folders) (Box 14)
      - Automation, 1962-1964, undated (Box 14)
      - Bibliography: Spatial studies, 1966 (Box 14)
      - Notes: (Box 14)
        - Miscellaneous, 1958-1966, undated (Box 14)
        - Poverty in the United States, 1960-1967, undated, (2 folders) (Box 14)
        - Research Techniques (examples), undated (Box 14)
        - Significance of Data, 1963-1968, undated (Box 14)
        - Sources of data, 1963, 1967-1968, undated (Box 14)
        - Statistical pitfalls, 1964, undated (Box 14)
        - Unemployment: Aggregate Demand Deficiency--or other causes, 1961-1965, undated (Box 14)
      - Readings, 1962-1964, undated (Box 14)
      - Student papers, 1965, 1967 (Box 14)
    - Theory of International Trade (EcD5, EcD60): (Box 14)
      - Exams, articles, syllabus, 1938-1959, undated, (2 folders) (Box 14)
      - Notes: (Box 14)
        - Adjustment in balance of payments, 1941-1960, undated (Box 14)
        - Comparative advantage, 1924-1960, undated (Box 14)
        - Dependent economy, 1947-1956, undated (Box 14)
        - Dotlar “Problem,” 1952-1960, undated (Box 14)
        - Elasticities in international trade, 1950-1957, undated (Box 14)
        - The Future of Our Trade with Europe, 1949, 1953 (Box 14)
        - Hume on foreign trade, 1931-1932, 1960, undated (Box 14)
        - Income distribution and International trade, also Heckscher and Ohlin material, 1949-1960, undated (Box 14)
        - International and inter-regional adjustment (Paish material), 1959-1960, undated (Box 14)
        - Lecture, correspondence: Comparative Advantage (Leontief Thesis), 1953-1960, undated (Box 14)
        - Mercantilism and foreign trade, 1932-1960, undated (Box 14)
        - Terms of trade, 1931-1963, undated (Box 14)
        - Thornton, Mill, Bastable, Iverson on financial adjustment, 1949-1957, undated (Box 14)
        - Transfer problem (in particular Ohlin, Keynes, Metzler), 1932-1960, undated (Box 14)
      - Opening lecture, 1951-1960 (Box 14)
      - Records of course, 1925-1949, undated (Box 14)
    - Tutorial Readings (EcC70): (Box 15)
      - American Discontent, 1957-1959, undated (Box 15)
      - Biographical items, 1958, undated (Box 15)
      - Book Censorship (also movies, press), 1958-1959, undated (Box 15)
      - Business Education, undated (Box 15)
      - Causes Celebres (Dreyfuss, etc.), 1948-1961, undated (Box 15)
      - Civil Liberties, 1957-1959, undated (Box 15)
      - Classical Literature and History, 1961, undated (Box 15)
      - Communism in U.S.A., 1957-1959, undated (Box 15)
      - European Travelers in U.S.A., 1958-1961, undated (Box 15)
      - Hiss Case and Harry White, 1950-1958, undated (Box 15)
      - Literature and American Political and Social Problems, 1958, undated (Box 15)
      - Medicine, hypnotism, and allied topics, 1961 (Box 15)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954-1961, undated (Box 15)
      - Protestant Reformation, Catholics, 1959-1961, undated (Box 15)
      - Psychology and Freud, undated (Box 15)
      - Russian situation, 1958, undated (Box 15)
      - Science and philosophy of science, 1954-1956, undated (Box 15)
      - Urban development and planning, 1961, undated (Box 15)
      - Westward movement, Turner thesis, 1958, undated (Box 15)
  - Committees (Box 15)
    - Budget, 1954 (Box 15)
    - Honor System, 1952-1964, undated (Box 15)
    - Parking, 1957-1961 (Box 15)
    - Retirement, 1963 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - 1958-1972 (Box 15)
    - Statistics, 1960-1961 (Box 15)
    - Mars lecture series, 1963-1966, undated (Box 15)
- Publications, 1857-1992, undated (bulk, 1940-1979). (Box 15)
  This largest series contains all of Fetter's formal writings, both published and unpublished, as well as published writings of interest to him. Published articles, book reviews, books, pamphlets, manuscripts, correspondence, serials, and clippings contained within seven subseries. Contains photocopied research material (RESTRICTED) and transcripts of copied archival material. All research and correspondence for the Articles and Pamphlets Sub-Series is in the Research on Published Articles and Pamphlets Sub-Series of the General Research Series.
  - Articles of Interest (Box 15)
    - 1857-1942, (11 folders) (Box 15)
    - 1943-1958, (16 folders) (Box 16)
    - 1958-1966, (13 folders) (Box 17)
    - 1966-1976, (15 folders) (Box 18)
    - 1976-1991, undated, (14 folders) (Box 19)
    - undated, (3 folders) (Box 20)
  - Book Reviews (Box 20)
    - 1933-1954, (13 folders) (Box 20)
    - 1956-1977, (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Clippings of Interest (Box 21)
    - Magazine, 1930-1991, undated (Box 21)
    - Newspaper, 1918-1991, n.d, (3 folders) (Box 21)
    - Obituaries, 1945-1990 (Box 21)
  - Government Documents of Interest (Box 21)
    - 1896-1973, (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Published Articles and Pamphlets (Box 21)
    - 1921-1942, (6 folders) (Box 21)
  - Published Books (Box 21)
    - 1940-1990, undated, (11 folders) (Box 22)
    - 1931, Monetary Inflation in Chile: (Box 22)
      - Book, 1931 (Box 22)
      - Book, Spanish edition, 1937 (Box 22)
      - Manuscript draft, 1929, Jan. (Box 22)
      - Research, Chilean debt, debt payment, 1891: Notes and correspondence (Box 22)
      - Reviews, 1931-1933, undated (Box 22)
      - Spanish edition, 1936-1939 (Box 22)
  - Restricted (Box 22)
    - Facing the Facts: (Box 23)
      - Book, 1932 (Box 23)
      - Correspondence, 1932-1940, undated (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous research, 1932, undated (Box 23)
    - Problems of New Cuba: (Box 23)
      - Book, 1935 (Box 23)
      - Book, Spanish edition, 1935 (Box 23)
      - Notes and general correspondence, 1934-1935, undated (Box 23)
    - Fiscal Policies and the American Economy, ed. Kenyon E. Poole; “International Aspects of Fiscal Policy” by Fetter, royalties, 1951 (Box 23)
    - The Irish Pound: (Box 23)
      - Bibliography, 1958, undated (Box 23)
      - Book, 1954-1955 (Box 23)
      - Bullion reports, undated (Box 23)
      - Correspondence, 1933-1956, (2 folders) (Box 23)
      - Research: (Box 23)
        - Absentee tax, 1951-1954, undated (Box 23)
        - Annual register, 1794-1804, undated (Box 23)
        - Currency research, undated, (2 folders) (Box 23)
        - Debates in Irish Parliament on Restriction, 1797 (Box 23)
        - General, 1793-1804 (Box 23)
        - Huskisson and Irish Affairs, undated (Box 23)
        - Ireland: Newspapers and Book of Minutes Papers, undated (Box 23)
        - Irish currency: Newspaper and public record, 1804 (Box 23)
        - Irish exchange rate, undated (Box 23)
    - The Irish Pound: (Box 24)
      - Research: (Box 24)
      - Irish situation, undated (Box 24)
      - Notes on articles and books, 1949-1951, undated (Box 24)
      - Reviews, reprints, publishing, 1933-1954, undated (Box 24)
      - Royalties, 1960, undated (Box 24)
    - Economic writings of Francis Horner in the Edinburgh Review: (Box 24)
      - Book, 1802-1806 (Box 24)
      - Correspondence reprints, 1955-1958, undated (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous research, 1956, undated (Box 24)
    - Economic writings of Francis Horner in the Edinburgh Review: (Box 24)
      - Research: (Box 24)
      - Horner letters, undated (Box 24)
      - LSE papers and memoirs, undated (Box 24)
    - Selected Economics of Thomas Attwood: (Box 24)
      - Birmingham, 1961-1963, undated (Box 24)
      - Book, 1964 (Box 24)
      - Correspondence, 1938-1937 (Box 24)
      - Letters of Thomas Attwood, undated (Box 24)
      - Manuscript correspondence, 1962-1964, undated (Box 24)
      - Manuscript research, 1804, undated (Box 24)
      - Research: (Box 24)
        - Attwood, Mathias, 1817 (Box 24)
        - Bibliography, 1941-1955, undated (Box 24)
        - Reprints, 1962-1963, undated (Box 24)
    - Development of British Monetary Orthodoxy: (Box 24)
      - Bibliography, books, pamphlets, 1965 (Box 24)
      - Book, 1965 (Box 24)
      - Correspondence: General, 1938-1973, undated (Box 24)
      - Manuscript correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 24)
      - Publication, 1963-1976, undated (Box 24)
      - Research: (Box 24)
        - Arbuthnot, George, undated (Box 24)
        - Attwood, Thomas, 1958-1966, undated (Box 24)
        - Bank of England: (Box 24)
          - 1955, undated (Box 24)
          - Bullion records, undated (Box 24)
          - Stock, 1954-1959, undated, (2 folders) (Box 24)
        - Bankruptcies, undated (Box 24)
        - British banking, undated (Box 24)
        - Cabinet memoranda in Great Britain, 1968-1989, undated (Box 24)
        - Endinburgh review, 1949-1955, undated (Box 24)
        - Hudson Gurnet papers, 1955, undated (Box 24)
        - Horner papers, 1954-1955, undated (Box 24)
    - Development of British Monetary Orthodoxy: (Box 25)
      - Research: (Box 25)
        - Huskisson speech and notes, undated (Box 25)
        - Liverpool, 1832, undated (Box 25)
        - Kings speeches, 1794-1875 (Box 25)
        - Miscellaneous: (Box 25)
          - Research notes, 1951-1957, undated, (3 folders) (Box 25)
          - Reviews, journals, and proceedings, 1958-1961, undated, (2 folders) (Box 25)
        - Monetary theory, 1938-1959, undated, (6 folders) (Box 25)
        - Murray, John, 1955, undated (Box 25)
        - Parliamentary: (Box 25)
          - History, 1922-1959, undated, (6 folders) (Box 25)
          - Reviews, 1955-1958, (2 folders) (Box 25)
          - Votes, undated (Box 25)
        - Silver classification, undated (Box 25)
        - Thornton, Samuel, undated (Box 25)
        - Treasury records, paymaster, foreign office, undated (Box 25)
        - Turner index, 1958-1959, undated (Box 25)
        - Votes in House of Lords, 1810, Mar. 2-1841, Oct. 1, (2 folders) (Box 25)
    - Development of British Monetary Orthodoxy: (Box 26)
      - Research: (Box 26)
        - Votes in House of Lords, 1842, Feb. 7-1868, May 28, (2 folders) (Box 26)
        - Votes in House of Parliament, 1804, Mar. 7-1833, Aug. 21, (3 folders) (Box 26)
      - Reviews, 1965-1966, undated (Box 26)
      - “The Transfer Problem: Formal Elegance or Historical Realism”: (Box 26)
        - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 26)
        - Notes and research, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Monetary and Financial Policy in 19th Century Britain: (Box 26)
      - Book, 1973 (Box 26)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box 26)
      - Research: Miscellaneous research, 1951-1972, undated (Box 26)
      - Reviews, 1974 (Box 26)
    - Economist in Parliament: (Box 26)
      - Book, 1980 (Box 26)
      - Correspondence in general, 1938-1977 (Box 26)
      - Criticism of manuscript, `1974, undated (Box 26)
      - Duke publication, 1978-1989 (Box 26)
      - Master list, lists, charts, abbreviations, undated (Box 26)
      - Partial manuscript, 1970, undated (Box 26)
      - Rejections, 1962-1976 (Box 26)
      - Research: (Box 26)
        - Basic lists: Commons, undated (Box 26)
        - Committee appointments by lords, undated (Box 26)
        - Committee by persons: (Box 26)
          - House of Commons, undated (Box 26)
          - Parliament, undated (Box 26)
        - Committee evidence, 1972, undated (Box 26)
        - Committees, undated (Box 26)
        - Commons journal, 1796-1868, undated, (6 folders) (Box 26)
        - Currency: Bank of England, undated (Box 26)
        - Election notes, undated (Box 26)
        - Electoral facts, undated (Box 26)
        - Factual comments on economists, undated (Box 26)
        - Factual comments of economists, undated (Box 27)
        - House of Lords votes, 1788, Dec. 26-1868, July 24, (2 folders) (Box 27)
        - Important votes, common, undated (Box 27)
        - List of speeches: (Box 27)
          - Vol. 1-193, PD 3rd series, undated, (5 folders) (Box 27)
          - Vol. 1-25 new series PD, undated (Box 27)
          - Vol. 22-41, undated (Box 27)